myfirstshow.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy, Privacy & Terms - Myfirstshow.com

Last updated on January 26th, 2019 at 10:26 am

Myfirstshow.com committed to protect privacy of all visitors of this website.

www.myfirstshow.com welcomes you. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we provide.

Skyhigh movies, LLC is the sole owner of the website www.myfirstshow.com (hereinafter “website”). The Policy is applicable to the website.

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavour to post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source and we will update in proper format.

**Information Collected by myfirstshow.com**

Information Collected by myfirstshow.com from several areas where members can submit information to us, and we also have features that automatically collect information from our members and other users to provide in proper way.

**Information provided to myfirstshow.com**

myfirstshow.com features certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us.

**Registration** : You may register with us to use some of our member only features on our site. We may also offer the option for you to register with us or sign up for our mailing list without having to use any other product or service. During registration, you provide your “contact information” (which identifies you and how we can contact you, such as your name and email address) as well as certain demographic information (which describes certain information about you, such as your country of residence). You may be asked to enter an e-mail address and password. We may also ask you to provide additional information about your music preferences, so that we can cater to those preferences.

**Communications from Us and Mailing Lists:** In order to keep our members informed about the operation of our services, we will send e-mails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our site and subscription service. For additional information about our site, services and offers, we give our members the option of joining our mailing list. We also allow you to choose whether to receive mails from partners and sponsors that we think will be of interest to you. Each marketing e-mail from us will come with instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

**Communications with Us:** We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contacting us with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

Interactive Features: We also may offer interactive features, such as message boards, chat rooms, etc. Note that all personal information you send or post via such features becomes public information, and we are not responsible for any information you choose to make public (including any online identifier, such as an email address, instant messenger name or member name). We may store such information in an aggregate form but we will not file or retain such information on a personal basis. We may monitor such traffic via electronic software or personnel but only to check for obscenity, defamation or other types of abusive language, which we reserve the right to remove at any time.

**Surveys:** We may occasionally ask members to participate in surveys. Such surveys will be voluntary. They are intended to improve your member experience and any information you provide we may associate with your member name for future use. Any personal information collected will be used only by us unless we specify otherwise, although we may share aggregate survey result information with others.

**Links:** We may display links to other sites within myfirstshow.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

The website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Skyhigh Movies, Inc. Please be aware that we, Skyhigh Movie, Inc. and/or the website, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and you tube links.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the website or to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. It does not apply to third party advertisements which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising & Third Party Cookies: **In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place cookies on your browser. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

With whom we share your information: We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

**Downloads:** We do link to other web sites which might support downloads. We are not responsible for the downloadable materials that are present in these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding the downloadable materials of these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding these downloads in the websites that our visitors refer to in our forums and discussions.

Downloads referred to in this privacy policy can be videos, images, software, games and any application files. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Your Privacy is our privacy!
